<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Trusted Tiny Things v2</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_overview">OverviewActivity</string>
    
     <string name="terms_conditions">   
        
        The Trusted Tiny Things (T3) project is aiming at investigating how some of the challenges inherent in making the Internet of Things (IoT) more transparent and trustworthy to users. The event is conducted by members of the dot.rural Digital Economy Hub at the University of Aberdeen. The key contact for the T3 project is Dr Edoardo Pignotti (<b><a href="mailto:e.pignotti@abdn.ac.uk">e.pignotti@abdn.ac.uk</a></b>).
       \n\n
        Data collected by the Trusted Tiny Things Software Platform is stored securely and password protected; our servers are located in a secure environment and server administration is handled only by members of University of Aberdeen staff working on the Trusted Tiny Things project. We strongly recommend that you keep alternative copies of your data as we will not be liable for loss or damage to data while it is stored within our systems.
     \n\n
        As part of the system we record and make use of you android device ID.  In our system, your device ID is associated with the devices you have interacted with and the capabilities you have accepted.
     \n\n
        We do not collect the content of the NFC (Near Field Communication) tags that you have scanned. Instead, we generate a unique ID for the tag in order to identify it.
      \n\n
        We will make use of the data generated by users only to support the academic research associated with the Trusted Tiny Things project. Selected elements of this research project may be subject to additional approval; we will seek consent from associated participants as appropriate.
      \n\n
        The Trusted Tiny Things Software Platform must not be used for any commercial purpose whatsoever or for any illegal or unauthorised purpose. When you use the Trusted Tiny Things Software Platform you must comply with all applicable UK laws relating to online conduct (including, without limitation, content which can be posted online) and with any applicable international laws, including the local laws in your country of residence.      
    \n\n
      Anyone can use this application simply by agreeing to these terms and conditions.  
      \n
      You may remove your information and content at any time, however, it is important to be aware that we may be unable to delete certain information associated  to devices but this data will instead be anonymised.  
      \n\n
      This service complies with the University of Aberdeen - Policy on Data Protection (http://www.abdn.ac.uk/staffnet/documents/policy-zone-governance-and-compliance/DPApolicy.pdf) and is governed by the University of Aberdeen - Conditions for using IT Facilities (http://www.abdn.ac.uk/staffnet/documents/policy-zone-information-policies/DIT_cond-IT.pdf).
    \n\n
     Note: please contact <b><a href="mailto:e.pignotti@abdn.ac.uk">e.pignotti@abdn.ac.uk</a></b> if you wish to use the Trusted Tiny Things Software Platform but do not wish to be included in our research.
        </string>
    
    
 <string name="scan">Please place your device close to the <b>NFC tag</b>, alternatively select from your collection of devices listed below.</string>
</resources>
